[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year was the film Steel Magnolias released?", "correct_answer": "1989", "incorrect_answers": ["1987", "1988", "1990"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the chemical symbol for Ytterbium?", "correct_answer": "Yb", "incorrect_answers": ["Ye", "Ym", "Yt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The atomic number of Zinc is 52.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The average US penny stays in circulation for 50 years.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who plays Alfred in the record breaking 2008 movie, The Dark Knight?", "correct_answer": "Michael Caine", "incorrect_answers": ["Aaron Eckhart", "Morgan Freeman", "Heath Ledger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not an actual breed of sheep?", "correct_answer": "Dakota", "incorrect_answers": ["Scottish black-face", "Hampshire", "Merino"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Complete the following line from the film Stripes:\nCaptain Stillman: [talking to himself; looking through binoculars, spying on female soldiers taking showers] Oh, God, I wish I was a ______.", "correct_answer": "loofah", "incorrect_answers": ["fly on the wall", "scrub brush", "woman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When a heterosexual couple has sex using a latex condom, what can create risk of HIV-infection?", "correct_answer": "Oil-based lubricants", "incorrect_answers": ["The condoms tentacles", "Nothing", "Water-based lubricants"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For its ability to reduce anxiety and tension, wine is considered to be this.", "correct_answer": "Natural tranquilizer", "incorrect_answers": ["Intoxicating", "Grappa Duve", "Controlled substance"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sharks are immune to cancer.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Female drivers have more traffic accidents on Friday the 13th.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie, Allies parents take her away in order to separate her from Noah. What else does Allies mother do to keep the young lovers apart?", "correct_answer": "She hides the letters Noah sends to Allie.", "incorrect_answers": ["She threatens Noah and forces him to leave the country.", "She tells Allie that Noah was killed in the war.", "She finds a fiance for Ally."]}]